<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://subdavis.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://subdavis.com/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-05-24T11:27:45-04:00</updated><id>https://subdavis.com/blog/</id><title type="html">Brandon’s blog</title><subtitle>Just a guy in a new city doin' a new thing.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Goals For The Summer</title><link href="https://subdavis.com/blog/jekyll/update/2017/05/23/summer-goals.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Goals For The Summer" /><published>2017-05-23T23:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-23T23:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://subdavis.com/blog/jekyll/update/2017/05/23/summer-goals</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://subdavis.com/blog/jekyll/update/2017/05/23/summer-goals.html">&lt;p&gt;A blog?!  I know it’s a bit 2005, so take a chill pill and let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have some serious free time ahead of me this summer.  I’m talking &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rotorway.com/&quot;&gt;build a helicopter in your back yard&lt;/a&gt; after retirement level shit.  And since I don’t have a pilot’s license (or for that matter a back yard) I figured it might be good to try and learn some new skills and contribute to society, or something like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of May, I’m moving to Washington D.C. to start a new job.  The catch is that the job doesn’t start until mid June, which gives me 6 weeks to kick back and watch the price is right &lt;em&gt;every day&lt;/em&gt;.  Except I hate the price is right, so I need a plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The plan (recently hatched by my starry-eyed, overzealous self) is to spend time each day learning, tinkering, or otherwise bettering myself or the world in some kind of way.  I’d like to set a few goals &lt;em&gt;in writing&lt;/em&gt; so that I may be publically shamed when, 6 weeks from now, all I have to show for my summer is an intimate knowlege of ABC’s LOST. Let’s do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set up a blog using &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;github pages&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;DONE&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Obtain the latest editions of CLRS and Cracking the Coding Interview.  If these seem like odd choices for someone who just landed a job, &lt;a href=&quot;http://lifehacker.com/the-company-you-work-for-is-not-your-friend-1692113529&quot;&gt;give this a read&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Continue contributing to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/perfectapi/CKP&quot;&gt;perfectapi/CKP&lt;/a&gt;.  I’m quite interested in cryptography and this project has been a great way to start learning what practical crypto looks like.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start looking into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/keepassxreboot/keepassxc&quot;&gt;keepassxc&lt;/a&gt; issue tracker.  Why doesn’t it support KDBX4 yet?!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Excercise often.  Don’t let all this techno crap get in the way of being healthy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get out and see the city, hike some, and enjoy the weekends.  There’s nothing like staying cooped up in a 700 sq. ft. apartment to keep morale and productivity high.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Read novels again.  Check out some of the titles from this year’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2017/5/20/15653006/nebula-awards-2016-winners-science-fiction-fantasy-charlie-jane-anders&quot;&gt;nebula awards&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn &lt;a href=&quot;https://golang.org/&quot;&gt;golang&lt;/a&gt; properly.  I’m an avid subscriber of trial-by-fire, so I’ll have to find another project suited for Go.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That seems like enough to keep me at least semi-busy.  In addition, I like to keep up with the NY Times, Adam Savage’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tested.com/&quot;&gt;Tested&lt;/a&gt;, ISS goings on, and binge old movies (I’ve been itching to watch Apollo 13 all week so perhaps that will happen soon).  As I get into these and other little projects, I will write more meaty posts about what I learn.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A blog?! I know it’s a bit 2005, so take a chill pill and let me explain.</summary></entry></feed>